well first off baj Finance has seen
strong growth on the customer franchise
uh standpoint what they've seen is from
five CR the customer franchise has risen
to six CR on a year on-ear basis q1 of
FY 23 has seen a growth of 27 lakh when
we're looking at it from a quarter
perspective and 98 lakh when we're
looking at it on a year-on-year
perspective so strong growth coming in
there in terms of number of loans as
well up it was at 46 lakh is the number
of loans disbursed in q1 of f 22 in q1
of FY 23 that's coming at 74 lakh so
strong growth there good Tailwind when
we're looking at AUM as well up above
that 2 lakh CR Mark in fact 2 lak 4,000
CR is where that AUM number has come in
at that's a 31% growth when I'm looking
at it year on year and the q1 fy2 23
Standalone number has come in at a shade
below 12,000 CR it's com in at 11,900 CR
so strong growth there the liquidity
Surplus continues to remain strong above
the 11,500 CR Mark the capital adequacy
to remains strong above 25% in fact
26.6% is where that is and uh the
company has informed that they've
invested 2500 CR even in its Housing
Finance um which is Bajaj housing
Housing Finance the deposit book growth
also continues uh unabated the deposit
book has grown from 28 uh 28,000 CR to
34,000 CR on a year on-year basis strong
growth across metrics for Bajaj Finance